headout.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy

This document represents a legal document that serves as our privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). It governs the privacy terms of our Website. Our Privacy Policy is part of our Legal Terms. Capitalized terms, unless otherwise defined below, have the meaning specified within the Definitions section our Terms of Use (https://www.headout.com/terms-of-use).

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on https://www.headout.com/privacy-policy.

## Your Privacy

Headout Inc. (“ **Headout** ”) follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information.

We break up the types of information you share into Non Personal Information and Personally Identifiable Information.

"Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser.

"Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within access to certain features of our Website. This can include information about your Entity as a Provider or as a Member when making purchases from a Provider. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your email address, physical location, business name, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you. It may also include any images that upload when using our Website as well as credit card or other payment information that you may present when making a purchase from a Provider through our Website ( **please note the important exception below under Online Purchases regarding payment information provided through our Website** ).

## Information We Collect

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to **Headout** when using our Website.

As a Visitor, you can browse our Website to find out more about our Website. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.

However, if registered as a Member, you must provide Personally Identifiable Information to **Headout** in order for us to provide you with certain features our Website. As a Member, we collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways:

### At Member Registration

When you register for membership, we collect your name and email address so that we can communicate with you about our Website.

### Participation in Our Website

You can upload Member Content as part of using our Website. You should take great care in what you may upload so as not to infringe on your own privacy or that of others. We don’t have a duty to review what you upload.

### Online Purchases

Members can make purchases of products/services from a Provider through our Website. The payment information you provide clearly contains Personally Identifiable Information. However, any payment information that you give to a Provider outside of our Website is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Online Forms

There may be online forms used in our Website. The information you enter into these online forms may contain Personally Identifiable Information.

## Computer Information Collected

When you use our Website, **Headout** automatically collects certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. **Headout** also collects the following:

### Cookies

Our Website uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

### Web Beacons

We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters (“Web Beacons”). The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails. Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website. We do not link Non Personal Information from the Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.

### Automatic Information

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the Website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the Website to which you’re headed when you leave our Website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website.

## How We Use Your Information

 **Headout** uses the information we receive from you as follows:

### Providing and Improving Our Website

 **Headout** may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to provide our Website to you as well as to make improvements to it.

### Communications and Email Alerts

When **Headout** communicates with you about our Website, we will use the email address you provided when registering as a Member. We may also send you Website alerts regarding your use of our Website. Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about **Headout** , unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time through your account. While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving Website alerts.

### Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties

 **Headout** does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. However, we may use demographic information for data aggregation purposes which might be sold to other parties at our discretion. Any such data aggregation would not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide Websites to **Headout** with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, webhosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective Websites and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.

### Community Discussion Boards

Our Website may offer the capability for Users to communicate with each other through online community discussion boards. **Headout** does not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards. If you chose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information through such postings.

### Legally Required Releases of Information

 **Headout** may be legally required to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of **Headout** , our Users, employees, and affiliates.

### Disclosures to Successors

If **Headout** is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would become responsible for providing the Website to you, we retain the right to transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business.

## Protecting Your Child’s Privacy

We want to protect your Child’s privacy. Even though our Website is not designed for use by a Child, we realize that a Child may attempt to access our Website. We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from a Child. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your Child is using our Website, please contact us. We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover on our own that a Child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are a Child, please do not access our Website.

## Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties

We believe in everyone’s right to privacy. If any Member Content you upload to our Website contain the images of third parties (i.e. bystanders), you need to make sure you have permission to include them in your image. While we are not legally liable for the actions of our Users, we will remove any images for which we are notified that such images violate the privacy rights of others.

## Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other websites (“Third Party Websites”). You agree that **Headout** has no control over such Third Party Websites and that such Third Party Websites are NOT subject to this Privacy Policy. These Third Party Websites may have their own privacy policies and other legal documents. It is your sole responsibility to verify the privacy policies and other legal documents of such Third Party Websites to see how they treat your personal information. You acknowledge that your use and access of these Websites is solely at your own risk.

## Our Email Policy

 **Headout** and our affiliates fully comply with international laws regarding SPAM. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from **Headout** and/or our affiliates. We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.

## Our Security Policy

 **Headout** has constructed our Website using industry standard encryption and authentication tools to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. When we collect your Personally Identifiable Information through our Website, we encrypt this information and attempt to prevent unauthorized access to it by using industry standard technologies, such as encryption software, routers and firewalls. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and to not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Website when not in use, especially if you are sharing a computer or mobile device with someone else or are using a public computer.

## Privacy Policy Updates

 **Headout** reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

## Changing Your Information

You may change your email address or other Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the account management features found on our Website.

## Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us by email at[privacy@headout.com](mailto:privacy@headout.com).

## Your California Privacy Rights

Your California Privacy Rights identifies the practices of **Headout** as they relate to the use and sharing of personal information about California residents collected through this website.

Under the law of the State of California, California residents who provide personal information via a website or other online service, such as this website, may request and obtain from **Headout** , once each calendar year, information about the personal information **Headout** shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. Where applicable, this information would include the categories of personal information, and the names and addresses of those businesses with which **Headout** shared personal information for the prior calendar year.

To obtain from **Headout** the information specified by California law, please contact:

By Mail: Headout Inc.  
Attn: CEO  
500 7th Avenue, Floor 17A  
New York, NY 10018  
By E-mail: hi@headout.com
